#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jim-kau-0aaa8473 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Microsoft Word

Microsoft Excel

Microsoft Power Point

## Languages

Chinese (Native or Bilingual)
Malay (Limited Working)
English (Professional Working)
Cantonese (Elementary)

# Jim Kau

E-commerce & Sales Executive

Johor Bahru

## Summary

The jobs have cultivated my positive manners and mindset; The job also gives the opportunity of inspired by others work's experience, skills and learning from each others. These helps me when deal with people or works.

I would say that "Working will not affect you badly but help you beneficially".

# Experience

Silver Planet Streetwear Sales Promoter January 2008 - June 2008 (6 months)

I was trained to be more initiative and friendly when deal with the customers in order to let them feel satisfied and have a great time while choosing their clothes. I learnt being able to work in a packed and pressure environment, fulled with numerous products. As a Sales Promoter, I have been paying lot of effort in order to hit the sales target efficiently. In addition, we were requested to arrange the "products" (clothes) in a proper way which made me to be more organised and considerate.

Jim In Enterprise

Cashier

January 2006 - October 2007 (1 year 10 months)

Collects the payment in cash for the goods or services exchanged, records the amount received, makes change, and issues receipts to customers. This is a job that let me learnt about how to communicate with customers and be more careful with the money issue. Sometimes, a good and comfortable relationship between promoter and customers may bring the benefit and good impression towards a shop/company.

# Education

Nottingham Trent University

Bachelor's degree, Graphic Design · (2009 - 2013)

KBU International College (KBU)

Bachelor's degree, Graphic Design · (2010 - 2013)

KBU International College (KBU)

Foundation degree, Art/Art Studies, General · (2008 - 2009)

SMK Taman Tun Aminah

Secondary, Science Stream · (2003 - 2007)